{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Alison, _______ the children come here at once!",
      "a": "you let",
      "b": "let you",
      "c": "let",
      "d": "tell",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I think you must _______ your parents know about it!",
      "a": "let",
      "b": "tell",
      "c": "you let",
      "d": "say",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Let somebody do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ forget that we have a date!",
      "a": "Let we",
      "b": "Let's not",
      "c": "Let wc not",
      "d": "Don't let we",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me...\n\n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mum,_______ go to the shops today!",
      "a": "don't we",
      "b": "let's not",
      "c": "let's no",
      "d": "don't let we",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Let do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mum, ______ a look at those dresses!",
      "a": "have you",
      "b": "have",
      "c": "you have",
      "d": "let you have",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Oh no! _______ me that.",
      "a": "You don't tell",
      "b": "Don't you tell",
      "c": "Not tell",
      "d": "Don't tell",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please, _______ those boys not to play here!",
      "a": "you tell",
      "b": "tell you",
      "c": "tell",
      "d": "let tell",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is going to try on the sweater, OK, _______ try it on!",
      "a": "let she",
      "b": "let her",
      "c": "tell her",
      "d": "tell she",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me...\n\n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Children, _______ in the garden, not in the house!",
      "a": "let you play",
      "b": "play you",
      "c": "you let play",
      "d": "play",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Come on girls, ______ do it today!",
      "a": "let you",
      "b": "let's",
      "c": "let we",
      "d": "we let us",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me...Â \n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}